Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. International Advertisements Collection, 1900-2004 and undated, bulk 1965-1990
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Latin America, 1928-2004 and undated (Box EU11)
  - Chile (Santiago Office) (Box LA2)
    - Unilever (Box LA3)
      - Rexona deodorant, 1980s (Box LA3)
      - Sedal styling mousse, 1988 (Box LA3)
      - Sunsilk hair care, 1984 (Box LA3)
    - Valle Nevado, 1989 (Box LA3)
    - Warner-Lambert (Box LA3)
      - Listerine, 1987 (Box LA3)
      - Lubriderm, 1987 (Box LA3)
      - Schick, 1982 (Box LA3)
  - Colombia (Bogotá Office) (Box LA3)
    - Betsey Clark School Supplies, 1987 (Box LA3)
    - [Cortabaco: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA3)
    - [Eastman Kodak: See Oversize Box OV8, Oversize Folder OF17] (Box LA3)
    - [Eli Lilly: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA3)
    - [Kraft: See Oversize Folder OF17] (Box LA3)
    - [Nestlé: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA3)
    - Parker Pen, circa 1986 (Box LA3)
    - [PepsiCo: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA3)
    - [Philips: See Oversize Box OV8, Oversize Folder OF17] (Box LA3)
    - [Sociedad Aeronautica de Medellin: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA3)
    - [Unilever: See Oversize Box OV8, Oversize Folder OF17] (Box LA3)
    - Warner-Lambert, 1987 (Box LA3)
  - Costa Rica (Undetermined Office) (Box LA3)
    - Kraft, 1998-1999 (Box LA3)
  - Ecuador (Box LA3)
    - Guayaquil Office (Box LA3)
      - R.J. Reynolds (Doral) cigarettes, 1984 (See also Oversize Box OV8) (Box LA4)
      - Unilever (Box LA4)
        [See also Detersil]
        - Impulse deodorant, 1984 (Box LA4)
        - Signal toothpaste, 1984 (Box LA4)
    - Undetermined Office (Box LA4)
      - Cafe Expresso, 1984 (See also Oversize Box OV8) (Box LA4)
      - Detersil laundry detergent, 1984 (Box LA4)
      - Industrie Buitoni Perugina Wafers (packaging designs), 1984 (Box LA4)
      - [R.J. Reynolds: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA4)
  - Jamaica (Kingston Office) (Box LA4)
    - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1938 (Box LA4)
  - Latin America (Continent-Wide Campaigns) (Box LA4)
    - Multiple Offices (Box LA4)
      - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1939 (Box LA4)
    - Undetermined Office (Box LA4)
      - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1957-1963, (2 folders) (Box LA4)
      - Eastman Kodak, consumer, 1961-1971, (4 folders) (Box LA4)
      - Eastman Kodak, trade, 1965-1969 (Box LA4)
      - RCA, 1961-1963, (2 folders) (Box LA4)
  - Mexico (Mexico City Office) (Box LA4)
    - Bacardi Corporation Ron Bacardi 1873 Solera, 1984 (Box LA4)
    - Cerveceria Cuauhtemac S.A. (Carta Blanca) Beer, 1984 (Box LA4)
    - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1962-1963 (Box LA4)
    - DeBeers, 1984 (See also Oversize Box OV8) (Box LA4)
    - Eastman Kodak (See also Oversize Box OV8) (Box LA4)
      - Kodacolor VR-G film, 1988 (Box LA4)
      - Kodak Cross camera, 1988 (Box LA4)
      - Kodak S100 camera, 1988 (Box LA4)
      - Kodak Sport camera, 1988 (Box LA4)
    - Ford (See also Oversize Box OV8) (Box LA4)
      - Fairlane, 1965-1966 (Box LA4)
      - Ford Exporting, 1965-1966 (Box LA4)
      - Mercury, 1965-1966 (Box LA4)
      - Taurus, undated (Box LA4)
      - Thunderbird, undated (Box LA4)
      - Topaz, 1984, 1988 (Box LA4)
    - General Electric washing machines, 1984 (Box LA4)
    - Hyatt International, 1987 (Box LA4)
    - Kellogg Company (Box LA4)
      - Corn Flakes, 1964, 1974 (Box LA4)
      - Corn Pops, 1987 (Box LA4)
      - Fruiti Lupis, 1987 (Box LA4)
      - Smak, 1987 (Box LA4)
    - Kraft (Box LA4)
      - Cheese Whiz, 1960s-1970s (Box LA4)
      - Mermelada, 1960s-1970s (Box LA4)
      - Philadelphia cream cheese, 1960s-1970s, 1998-1999, (2 folders) (Box LA4)
    - Reckitt-Colman (Gerber), 1982 (Box LA4)
    - Standard Brands (Flan Royal), 1958 (Box LA4)
      [See also listings for Nabisco Brands in other countries]
  - Panama (Panama City Office) (Box LA4)
    - Eastman Kodak Duo Pack (with documentation), 1988 (Box LA4)
    - Kraft, 1998-1999 (Box LA4)
  - Puerto Rico (San Juan Office) (Box LA4)
    - Pan American World Airlines, 1969 (Box LA4)
    - R.J. Reynolds (Winston) cigarettes, 1984 (Box LA4)
  - Peru (Undetermined Office) (Box LA4)
    - [Coats Platons: See Oversize Box OV8 (Box LA4)
    - [Molinas Mayo: See Oversize Box OV8 (Box LA4)
  - Uruguay (Montevideo Office) (Box LA4)
    - [International Gold Association: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA4)
    - Nabisco Brands (Box LA4)
      [See also Standard Brands for other countries]
      - Chantilly Royal desserts, 1980s (Box LA4)
      - Royarina desserts, 1980s (Box LA4)
    - Parke-Davis (Ponstil), 1984 (Box LA4)
    - S.C. Johnson (Sheen) wax, 1984 (Box LA4)
  - Venezuela (Caracas Office) (Box LA4)
    - Champion Spark Plug (Anco wipers), 1984 (Box LA4)
    - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1962-1963 (Box LA4)
    - [Ford: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA4)
    - [Kraft: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA4)
    - Metropolitan de Automoviles car sales, 1984 (Box LA4)
    - [Philips: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA4)
    - Standard Brands, Flan Royal, 1950s-1960s (Box LA4)
    - Sunbeam Appliance Company (Oster), 1989 (Box LA4)
- Oversize Materials (Box LA4)
  - Africa (Box LA4)
    - South Africa (Box OV1)
      - Cape Town Office (Box OV1)
        - Stellenbosch Farmers Winery, 1980 (Box OV1)
      - Johannesburg Office (Box OV1)
        - Barclays, 1981 (Box OV1)
        - Ford, 1990 (Box OV1)
        - ICL, 1984 (Box OV1)
        - Kraft, 1990 (Box OV1)
        - Seiko, 1985 (Box OV1)
        - Unilever, 1974 (Box OV1)
      - Undetermined Office (Box OV1)
        - American Chamber of Commerce in South Africa (AMCHAM), 1986 (Box OV1)
        - United, 1979 (Box OV1)
  - Asia/Pacific (Box OV1)
    - China (Hong Kong Office) (Box OV2)
      - Agnes Long Wooton, 1988 (Box OV2)
      - Alfa-Romeo, 1987 (Box OV2)
      - British Railways, 1987-1989 (Box OV2)
      - Citicorp, 1990 (Box OV2)
      - Eastman Kodak, 1989 (Box OV2)
      - Ford, 1989, 1996 (Box OV2)
      - IBM, 1989-1990 (Box OV2)
      - Motorola, undated (Box OV2)
      - Nestlé, 1989-1990 (Box OV2)
      - Pearl and Dean, 1989 (Box OV2)
      - PepsiCo, 1987 (Box OV2)
      - Purolator Courier, 1985 (Box OV2)
      - R.J. Reynolds, 1988 (Box OV2)
      - Standard Chartered Bank, 1988-1989 (Box OV2)
    - India (Box OV2)
      - Bombay (Mumbai) Office (Box OV2)
        - Ministry of Health, Family Planning, and Urban Development, 1968 (Box OV2)
      - New Delhi Office (Box OV2)
        - Nestlé, 1990 (Box OV2)
    - Indonesia (Jakarta Office) (Box OV2)
      - Eastman Kodak, 1989 (Box OV2)
    - Japan (Tokyo Office) (Box OV2)
      - American Drug Corporation, 1988-1989 (Box OV2)
      - DeBeers Consolidated Mines, 1982-1985, 1987-1990 (Box OV2)
      - Ford, 1989 (Box OV2)
      - International Wool Secretariat, 1982-1985 (Box OV2)
      - Jaguar, 1996 (Box OV2)
      - Marubeni Corporation, 1988 (Box OV2)
      - R.J. Reynolds, 1988 (Box OV2)
      - Rolex, 1986 (Box OV2)
      - Rowntree Mackintosh, 1990 (Box OV2)
      - Rustenberg Platinum Mines, 1984 (Box OV2)
      - Suchiro Shuzo, 1989-1990 (Box OV2)
      - Unkai Shuzo, 1989 (Box OV2)
      - Warner-Lambert, 1990 (Box OV2)
    - Korea (Seoul Office) (Box OV2)
      - Ford, 1996 (Box OV2)
    - Malaysia (Kuala Lumpur Office) (Box OV2)
      - IBM, 1987 (Box OV2)
      - R.J. Reynolds, 1988 (Box OV2)
    - Philippines (Manila Office) (Box OV3)
      - Araneta Center, circa 1980s (Box OV3)
      - Citicorp, newspaper, 1987-1988 (Box OV3)
      - Eastman Kodak, circa 1980s-1990 (Box OV3)
      - IBM, 1989 (Box OV3)
      - Jourdan et Cie, circa 1988 (Box OV3)
      - Land Bank of the Philippines, 1987-1988 (Box OV3)
      - Matsushita Electric Industrial Company, 1988 (Box OV3)
      - PepsiCo, 1981 (Box OV3)
      - Philips, 1990 (Box OV3)
      - Pure Foods, 1984 (Box OV3)
      - Royal Dutch Petroleum Company, calendar, 1988 (Box OV3)
      - RubberWorld, 1987 (Box OV3)
      - S.C. Johnson and Son, 1987 (Box OV3)
      - Unilever, 1987-1988 (Box OV3)
      - Warner-Lambert, 1988 (Box OV3)
    - Singapore Office (Box OV3)
      - ABN Bank (Algemene Bank Nederland), 1988 (Box OV3)
      - Citicorp, 1990 (Box OV3)
      - Fraser and Neave Group, 1984 (Box OV3)
      - Holiday Inn, 1990 (Box OV3)
      - IBM, 1990 (Box OV3)
      - Metro Group, 1990 (Box OV3)
      - Times Publishing Group, 1987, 1990 (Box OV3)
      - Tokyu Group, 1985 (Box OV3)
    - Sri Lanka (Colombo Office) (Box OV3)
      - Unilever, 1985 (Box OV3)
    - Thailand (Bangkok Office) (Box OV3)
      - Eastman Kodak, 1989 (Box OV3)
      - IBM, 1989 (Box OV3)
      - Mitsubishi, 1989 (Box OV3)
      - Post Publishing, 1989 (Box OV3)
      - President Park, 1989-1990 (Box OV3)
      - S.C. Johnson and Son, 1987 (Box OV3)
      - Singer Company, 1989 (Box OV3)
      - Unifab, 1989 (Box OV3)
    - Australia (Box OV3)
      - Melbourne Office (Box OV3)
        - National Australia Bank, 1988 (Box OV3)
        - Scott Paper Company, 1985 (Box OV3)
      - Sydney Office (Box OV3)
        - Australia Writers and Art Directors Association, 1987 (Box OV3)
        - J. Walter Thompson Company, circa 1984 (Box OV3)
        - Wittington Investments Ltd., 1988 (Box OV3)
    - New Zealand (Box OV3)
      - Auckland Office (Box OV3)
        - New Zealand Cooperative Pig Market Association, 1984 (Box OV3)
      - Wellington Office (Box OV3)
        - Brooklyn Bakeries, 1984 (Box OV3)
        - IBM, 1988 (Box OV3)
        - Inland Revenue Department, 1988 (Box OV3)
      - Undetermined Office (Box OV3)
        - Breadmill, 1984 (Box OV3)
        - Club Med, 1984 (Box OV3)
  - Canada (Box OV3)
    - Montreal Office (Box OV4)
      - ALCAN Aluminum Ltd., 1990 (Box OV4)
      - Allied Chemical (Barrett Products), 1954 (Box OV4)
      - Aquascatum, 1959 (Box OV4)
      - Canadair, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box OV4)
      - Grand Themes, 1976 (Box OV4)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1969, 1984 (Box OV4)
      - Kraft (Box OV4)
        - Canadian cheese slices, 1961-1962, 1970 (Box OV4)
        - Miracle Whip, 1958, 1960, 1962, 1970-1973 (Box OV4)
        - Various, consumer magazine, 1958, 1961-1966, 1968-1974, 1977, (4 folders) (Box OV4)
        - Various, consumer newspaper, 1970-1975 (Box OV4)
      - Northern Telecom, 1974, 1976 (Box OV4)
      - PepsiCo, 1967 (Box OV4)
      - RCA Victor, 1960-1975, (4 folders) (Box OV4)
      - Reader's Digest, 1961, 1965, 1982, (2 folders) (Box OV4)
      - Robin Hood multiple foods, 1971 (Box OV4)
      - Scott Paper, 1972 (Box OV4)
      - Singer, 1963-1965, 1969-1973, (2 folders) (Box OV4)
      - Standard Brands, 1968 (Box OV4)
      - Terrasses, Les, 1976 (Box OV4)
    - Toronto Office (Box OV5)
      - Ford, 1977 (Box OV5)
      - IBM, 1983, 1985 (Box OV5)
      - Labatts, 1984 (Box OV5)
      - Mattel Inc., 1988 (Box OV5)
      - Mead Johnson, 1961 (Box OV5)
      - Northern Telecom (Bell Canada Enterprises), 1987-1988 (Box OV5)
      - PepsiCo, 1988 (Box OV5)
      - R.J. Reynolds, 1988 (Box OV5)
      - Teledyne, 1989 (Box OV5)
      - Toshiba, 1988 (Box OV5)
      - Warner-Lambert, 1988-1990 (Box OV5)
    - Vancouver Office (Box OV5)
      - Labatt, John, Ltd., 1984 (Box OV5)
      - Scott Paper Company, 1970s, 1983 (Box OV5)
  - Europe (Box OV5)
    - Belgium (Undetermined Office; Advertisements in French and Flemish) (Box OV6)
      - Gillette, 1969 (Box OV6)
      - I.C.L. Ltd., 1984 (Box OV6)
      - More O'Ferrall, 1984-1987 (Box OV6)
      - Philips, 1985 (Box OV6)
      - Toyota, 1988-1990 (Box OV6)
    - Denmark (Copenhagen Office) (Box OV6)
      - Codan A/S, 1985 (Box OV6)
      - Commodore International Ltd., 1985 (Box OV6)
      - Computerland, 1984 (Box OV6)
      - Ford, 1985 (Box OV6)
    - Finland (Helsinki Office) (Box OV6)
      - Rolex, 1986 (Box OV6)
    - France (Paris Office) (Box OV6)
      - Accor, 1984 (Box OV6)
      - Chesebrough-Pond's, circa 1981 (Box OV6)
      - Banque Robeco, 1997 (Box OV6)
      - Brother, 1991 (Box OV6)
      - DeBeers Consolidated Mines, 1980s (Box OV6)
      - Ford, 1987 (Box OV6)
      - Gazelle, 1986-1987 (Box OV6)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company, ca, 1960, 1987 (Box OV6)
      - Nadine Samson, 1986-1987 (Box OV6)
      - Penchinal, circa 1985 (Box OV6)
      - Point P, 1982 (Box OV6)
      - R.J. Reynolds, 1990 (Box OV6)
      - Val Thoreus, 1982 (Box OV6)
    - Germany (Box OV6)
      - Frankfurt Office (Box OV6)
        - Pillsbury, 1984 (Box OV6)
        - Pit Stop, 1986 (Box OV6)
      - Hamburg Office (Box OV6)
        - Schleswig Holstein Tourism, circa 1987 (Box OV6)
    - Greece (Athens Office) (Box OV6)
      - Tanagraia, 1989 (Box OV6)
    - Italy (Box OV6)
      - Milan Office (Box OV6)
        - Black and Decker, 1984 (Box OV6)
        - DeBeers Consolidated Mines, 1982, 1985 (Box OV6)
        - Ford, 1984 (Box OV6)
        - Griguasco, 1982-1984 (Box OV6)
        - Kraft, 1986-1990 (Box OV6)
        - Matsushita (Technics), 1989 (Box OV6)
        - Rizzoli Editore S.P.A., 1987 (Box OV6)
        - Sitia Yuomo, 1987 (Box OV6)
        - Standard Brands, 1965 (Box OV6)
        - Unilever, 1987 (Box OV6)
      - Rome Office (Box OV6)
        - Alitalia, 1988 (Box OV6)
        - Citicorp, 1988 (Box OV6)
    - Netherlands (Amsterdam Office) (Box OV6)
      - BMW, 1996 (Box OV6)
      - Eastman Kodak, circa 1980 (Box OV6)
      - Unilever, circa 1980 (Box OV6)
    - Portugal (Lisbon Office) (Box OV6)
      - Refrigor, 1992 (Box OV6)
      - Secretaria de Estado da Cultura, Direccao Geral da Accao Cultural, 1990 (Box OV6)
    - Spain (Madrid Office) (Box OV6)
      - Banco Hispano Americano, 1984 (Box OV6)
      - DeBeers Consolidated Mines, Ltd., 1988 (Box OV6)
      - Eastman Kodak, 1976 (Box OV6)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company, circa 1976 (Box OV6)
      - Ministry of Agriculture, 1988 (Box OV6)
      - Nestlé, 1976 (Box OV6)
      - R.J. Reynolds, 1988 (Box OV6)
    - Sweden (Stockholm Office) (Box OV7)
      - Annousbolaget, 1989 (Box OV7)
      - Arlanda Auport, 1989 (Box OV7)
      - Kemetyl, 1988 (Box OV7)
      - Marinstaben, 1982 (Box OV7)
    - Switzerland (Zurich Office) (Box OV7)
      - Aer Lingus, 1988 (Box OV7)
      - AES (Schweiz) Ag., 1981 (Box OV7)
      - R.J. Reynolds, 1987-1988 (Box OV7)
      - Sacom SA, circa 1987 (Box OV7)
    - Turkey (Istanbul Office) (Box OV7)
      - Altinyildiz, circa 1989 (Box OV7)
      - IBM, circa 1989 (Box OV7)
    - United Kingdom (Box OV7)
      - London Office (Box OV7)
        - ALCAN, 1968 (Box OV7)
        - Allied Lyons PLC, 1984-1985, 1988 (Box OV7)
        - British Airport Authority, 1987 (Box OV7)
        - British Telecommunications System, 1985-1988 (Box OV7)
        - Chesebrough-Pond's, newspaper, 1962 (Box OV7)
        - DeBeers Consolidated Mines, Ltd., 1987, 1999 (Box OV7)
        - Eastman Kodak, newspaper, circa 1960s (Box OV7)
        - Hi-Tee, 1990 (Box OV7)
        - ITV Association, 1989-1990 (Box OV7)
        - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1982 (Box OV7)
        - J&B scotch whiskey, 1999 (Box OV7)
        - Jaguar, 1999 (Box OV7)
        - Kellogg Company, 1987 (Box OV7)
        - Madame Tussaud's, 1999 (Box OV7)
        - Muscular Dystrophy, 1984 (Box OV7)
        - National Westminster Bank, 1984, 1989 (Box OV7)
        - The Observer, Ltd., 1987 (Box OV7)
        - Parker Pen, 1989 (Box OV7)
        - Reader's Digest, 1991 (Box OV7)
        - Rowntree Mackintosh (includes Kit Kat), 1984-1999 (Box OV7)
        - Royal Air Force (Central Office information), 1984 (Box OV7)
        - Silhouette, 1970 (Box OV7)
        - Trustee Savings Bank Association, 1980s (Box OV7)
        - Tycom Corporation, 1982 (Box OV7)
        - Unilever (including Persil), 1984-1990 (Box OV7)
        - Warner-Lambert, 1984 (Box OV7)
      - Manchester Office (Box OV7)
        - ASDA, circa 1984 (Box OV7)
        - British Gas NorthEastern, 1989 (Box OV7)
        - Co-Operative Retail Services, 1989 (Box OV7)
        - Greenwall Whitley Group PLC, circa 1984-1985 (Box OV7)
        - Guardian and Manchester Evening News PLC, 1989 (Box OV7)
        - National Westminster Bank PLC, 1987 (Box OV7)
        - Norcross Ltd. UK, 1989 (Box OV7)
        - Piccadily Radio, circa 1984 (Box OV7)
        - Sharp Electronics, 1989-1991 (Box OV7)
  - Latin America (Box OV7)
    - Argentina (Buenos Aires Office) (Box OV8)
      - Exxon, 1991 (Box OV8)
    - Brazil (Box OV8)
      - Rio De Janeiro Office (Box OV8)
        - CitiBank, 1984 (Box OV8)
        - PepsiCo, 1987 (Box OV8)
        - Nabisco Brands, 1989 (Box OV8)
      - São Paulo Office (Box OV8)
        - Champion spark plug, 1988 (Box OV8)
        - CitiBank, 1984 (Box OV8)
        - Eastman Kodak, 1987-1988 (Box OV8)
        - Ford, 1984 (Box OV8)
        - Philips Ltd., 1988 (Box OV8)
        - Unilever, 1988 (Box OV8)
      - Undetermined Office (Box OV8)
        - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1962 (Box OV8)
        - Cigarros Souza Cruz, 1969 (Box OV8)
    - Chile (Santiago Office) (Box OV8)
      - Banco O'Higgins, 1989 (Box OV8)
      - Compana de Papeles y Cartones, 1989 (Box OV8)
      - Prompan, 1989 (Box OV8)
    - Colombia (Bogotá Office) (Box OV8)
      - Coltabaco, circa 1987 (Box OV8)
      - Eastman Kodak, 1970s-1980s (Box OV8)
      - Eli Lilly, circa 1980s (Box OV8)
      - Nestlé, 1970s-1980s (Box OV8)
      - PepsiCo, 1985 (Box OV8)
      - Philips, 1960-1974 (Box OV8)
      - Soc. Aeronautica de Medellin, circa 1987 (Box OV8)
      - Unilever, 1970s-1980s (Box OV8)
    - Ecuador (Guayaquil Office) (Box OV8)
      - Cafe Expresso, 1984 (Box OV8)
      - R.J. Reynolds, 1984 (Box OV8)
    - Mexico (Mexico City Office) (Box OV8)
      - DeBeers Consolidated Mines Ltd., 1984 (Box OV8)
      - Eastman Kodak, 1988 (Box OV8)
      - Ford, circa 1962, 1988-1989 (Box OV8)
    - Peru (Undetermined Office) (Box OV8)
      - Coats Platons (Hilos Cadena Llave SA) Patrica, 1984 (Box OV8)
      - Molinas Mayo (Avicola San Fernando), 1984 (Box OV8)
    - Uruguay (Montevideo Office) (Box OV8)
      - International Gold Association, circa 1984 (Box OV8)
    - Venezuela (Caracas Office) (Box OV8)
      - Ford, 1984 (Box OV8)
      - Kraft, circa 1964 (Box OV8)
      - Philips, 1989 (Box OV8)
- Oversize Folders (Box OV8)
  - Asia/Pacific (Box OV8)
    - China (Hong Kong Office) (Opaperfolder OF1, Box OV8)
      - IBM, 1989 (Box OV8)
    - China (Hong Kong Office) (Opaperfolder OF1, Box OV8)
      - Scott tissue, 1990s (Opaperfolder OF2, Box OV8)
    - Japan (Tokyo Office) (Opaperfolder OF3, Box OV8)
      - American Drug Corporation, 1990 (Box OV8)
      - Asahi beer, 1984 (Box OV8)
      - Burroughs, 1984 (Box OV8)
      - Chiyoda Ear, Nose and Throat Clinic, circa 1950 (Box OV8)
      - Daniel Diamond Legziel, 1982 (Box OV8)
      - Pepsico, 1982 (Box OV8)
      - Suchiro Shuzo, 1990 (Box OV8)
    - Malaysia (Kuala Lumpur Office) (Opaperfolder OF4, Box OV8)
      - Winston Network (R.J. Reynolds), 1985 (Box OV8)
    - Philippines (Manila Office) (Opaperfolder OF4, Box OV8)
      - Kraft (Arts and Kraft Summer Workshop, Cheddar, Cheez Whiz, Mayonnaise, Miracle Whip, Peanut Butter, Tang), 1998-2003 (Box OV8)
    - Singapore Office (Opaperfolder OF5, Box OV8)
      - Fraser & Neave Group, 1984 (Box OV8)
    - Taiwan (Taipei Office) (Opaperfolder OF6, Box OV8)
      - Citicorp, 1989 (Box OV8)
    - Thailand (Bangkok Office) (Opaperfolder OF7, Box OV8)
      - Warner-Lambert (Listerine), 1997 (Box OV8)
    - United Arab Emirates (Dubai Office) (Opaperfolder OF8, Box OV8)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company, circa 1980s (Box OV8)
    - New Zealand (Wellington Office) (Opaperfolder OF9, Box OV8)
      - ANZ Bank, 1984 (Box OV8)
  - Canada (Box OV8)
    - Montreal Office (Opaperfolder OF10, Box OV8)
      - Greb Industries (Warrington Products), 1984 (Box OV8)
    - Toronto Office (Opaperfolder OF11, Box OV8)
      - Toshiba, 1989 (Box OV8)
    - Vancouver Office (Opaperfolder OF11, Box OV8)
      - Scott Paper Company (Box OV8)
        - General, 1975 (Box OV8)
        - Baby Fresh, 1981-1990 (Box OV8)
        - Confidets, 1971-1982 (Box OV8)
        - Confidets News, 1972-1984 (Box OV8)
    - Multiple Offices (Opaperfolder OF11, Box OV8)
      - Labatt's, 1982 (Box OV8)
  - Europe (Box OV8)
    - Belgium (Brussels Office) (Opaperfolder OF12, Box OV8)
      - Lever Brothers (Coral detergent), 1991 (Box OV8)
    - France (Lyon Office) (Opaperfolder OF12, Box OV8)
      - Euro Advertising, undated (Box OV8)
      - Farmicredit, 1982 (Box OV8)
    - Portugal (Lisbon Office) (Opaperfolder OF12, Box OV8)
      - Proleite/Mimosa (UNICEF), 1992 (Box OV8)
      - Sogrape (Mateus), 1992 (Box OV8)
    - Romania (Bucharest Office) (Opaperfolder OF13, Box OV8)
      - Jacobs, 1999 (Box OV8)
      - Tragerile Loteriei de State, 1930s (Box OV8)
    - Spain (Madrid Office) (Opaperfolder OF14, Box OV8)
      - Eastman-Kodak, 1974, 1977 (Box OV8)
      - Kraft, 1976 (Box OV8)
      - R.J. Reynolds, 1989 (Box OV8)
    - United Kingdom (London Office) (Opaperfolder OF15, Box OV8)
      - Grundig, 1968 (Box OV8)
      - R.J. Reynolds, 1984 (Box OV8)
      - Rowntree Mackintosh, 1984 (Box OV8)
      - Singer, circa 1980 (Box OV8)
  - Latin America (Box OV8)
    - Brazil (São Paulo Office) (Opaperfolder OF16, Box OV8)
      - Eastman-Kodak, 1980s (Box OV8)
      - Philips, 1984-1985 (Box OV8)
    - Colombia (Bogotá Office) (Opaperfolder OF17, Box OV8)
      - Eastman-Kodak, circa 1964-1970, 1980s (Box OV8)
      - Kraft, circa 1964-1970 (Box OV8)
      - Philips, circa 1964-1970 (Box OV8)
      - Unilever, undated (Box OV8)
- Mounted Advertisements Series, circa 1919-1998 and undated (Box OV8)
  - Africa (Box OV8)
    - South Africa (Box OV8)
      - Jacobs coffee, undated (Box MAF1)
      - Kraft--Miracle Whip, undated (Box MAF1)
      - Petz Pamper cat food, 1988 (Box MAF1)
  - Asia-Pacific (Box MAF1)
    - General (Box MAF1)
      - Bisquit cognac, 1987 (Box MAP1)
      - DeBeers, 1989, 1996 (Box MAP1)
      - Eastman Kodak, 1988-1989 (Box MAP1)
      - Ford, 1964 (Box MAP1)
      - Ford, 1987 and undated (Box MAP1)
      - Grand Hyatt Hong Kong, 1989 (Box MAP1)
      - Hyatt Hotels, 1988 (Box MAP2)
      - IBM, 1987-1988 (Box MAP2)
      - Jade Animations Productions Limited, 1988 (Box MAP2)
      - Kraft--Philadelphia Cream Cheese, undated (Box MAP2)
      - Lever--Lux, 1989 (Box MAP2)
      - Lever--Sunsilk, 1988-1989 (Box MAP2)
      - Nestlé Nestomalt, undated (Box MAP2)
      - Pearl & Dean outdoor advertising, 1988 (Box MAP2)
      - Philips, 1988 (Box MAP2)
      - R. J. Reynolds--Salem, 1989 (Box MAP2)
      - Rolex, undated (Box MAP2)
      - Scott Paper--Cut-Rite was paper, 1987 (Box MAP2)
      - Sirdar Knits (Coats Patons Ltd.), 1988 (Box MAP2)
      - Smith Family Winter Appeal, 1988 (Box MAP2)
      - Tai Ping carpets, 1988 (Box MAP2)
      - Thai Farmers' Bank, 1988 (Box MAP2)
      - Tomco 501 Soap, undated (Box MAP2)
      - Unilever--Pepsodent, 1988 (Box MAP2)
      - Vauxhall, 1930s (Box MAP2)
      - Warner-Lambert Lubriderm, 1988 (Box MAP2)
      - Wedgwood, 1988 (Box MAP2)
    - Tokyo Office (Box MAP2)
      - DeBeers, 1987-1996 (Box MAP3)
      - R. J. Reynolds--Salem, 1988 (Box MAP3)
      - Suntory Martell, 1988 (Box MAP3)
    - Oversize (Box MAP3)
      - Warner-Lambert Listerine, 1997 (Opaperfolder MAP-OF1, Box MAP3)
  - Canada (Box MAP3)
    - General (Box MAP3)
      - Adams--Chiclets, 1988-1990 (Box MCA1)
      - Andrew Jergins (skin you love to touch), circa 1919 (Box MCA1)
      - Bull's Eye sauce, undated (Box MCA1)
      - Canadair, 1990 (Box MCA1)
      - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1925 (Box MCA1)
      - Ford, 1958, 1977 (Box MCA1)
      - Foster's Lager, 1988 (Box MCA1)
      - Gibson's Finest whiskey, 1990 (Box MCA1)
      - Kraft, 1987-1990 and undated (Box MCA1)
      - Lever--Lux, circa 1920 (Box MCA1)
      - MacDonald cigarettes, 1988 (Box MCA1)
      - Northern Telecom, 1988 (Box MCA1)
      - Oxo bouillon, 1987 (Box MCA1)
      - Pepsi-Cola, 1988 (Box MCA1)